[{"question":"What’s the percentage of colorblind men and women?","correct_choice":"8% of men / 1% of women","choices":["15% of men / 10% of women","8% of men / 1% of women","3% of men / 8% of women"," 8% of men / 8% of women"],"correct_answer_description":"Most colourblind people have difficulty with red-greens or blue yellows. This is why colour should not be the only way of organising content. "},{"question":"How wide is the ideal search box?","correct_choice":"27 characters wide","choices":["18 characters wide","22 characters wide","35 characters wide","27 characters wide"],"correct_answer_description":"According to studies, a 27 character search box helps accommodate 90% of search queries (Jakob Nielsen)."},{"question":"What’s the average number of items our working memory can hold?","correct_choice":"7 items","choices":["9 items","12 items","4 items","7 items"],"correct_answer_description":"7 ± 2 to be exact. This is why we try to keep navigation or menus under 7-9 items (George Miller)."},{"question":"Which of the following is not a recognized reading pattern?","correct_choice":"V-Shape","choices":["Z-Shape","V-Shape","Gutenberg diagram","F-Shape"],"correct_answer_description":"F-Shape is for search results, Z-Shape is inherited from print and Gutenberg is the main for Web (Steven Bradley)."},{"question":"What is banner blindness?","correct_choice":"Users completely ignoring banners","choices":["Too many banners on a single page","Blinking banners causing sight issues","Users completely ignoring banners","A trend"],"correct_answer_description":"Banner efficiency is decreasing. More and more people are consciously or unconsciously stopping to see them."},{"question":"What’s the maximum number of clicks required to find info on a good Website?","correct_choice":"It doesn’t matter","choices":["4","5","It doesn’t matter","3"],"correct_answer_description":"It’s not the number of clicks that matters, but rather how hard each click is (Steve Krug)."},{"question":"What is Malkovich Bias?","correct_choice":"Thinking everyone uses the Web like us","choices":["Thinking we know better than users","Thinking that you can’t trust anyone","Thinking we’re the center of the world","Thinking everyone uses the Web like us"],"correct_answer_description":"We tend to assume that other people use technology the way we do."},{"question":"Besides a movie, what is Wizard of Oz?","correct_choice":"A user testing method","choices":["A design principle","A usability problem","A brainstorming technique","A user testing method"],"correct_answer_description":"User-based evaluation of unimplemented technology where a human or team is simulating some or all the responses of the system."},{"question":"Why is it harder to remove features than to add features?","correct_choice":"Losing makes us 2x as miserable as gaining","choices":["People often use them in unexpected ways","Losing makes us 2x as miserable as gaining","Expert users love using all features","Features are often tied together"],"correct_answer_description":"Loss aversion states that losing something makes us twice as miserable as gaining the same thing makes us happy."},{"question":"How fast should a system respond in order to feel natural?","correct_choice":"Under 50 milliseconds","choices":["Under 1 second","Under 200 milliseconds","Under 2 seconds","Under 50 milliseconds"],"correct_answer_description":"A system stops feeling responsive if it takes more than 100 milliseconds for it to respond (Jakob Nielsen)."}]